http://www.crf-usa.org/donors/donor-privacy-policy

Log in
Sign in with FacebookSign in with GoogleSign in with Windows Live
Forgot Login?
Sign up
Articles
Donor Privacy Policy
Donor Privacy Policy
Constitutional Rights Foundation (“CRF") is a non-partisan, nonprofit organization classified as a tax-exempt organization under Section 501(c)(3) of the Internal Revenue Code.
This Donor Privacy Policy describes CRF's policies and practices with regard to the personal information we collect from our donors, volunteers, and supporters. This Donor Privacy Policy shall apply to the collection of information, both online and offline, including information collected through any of our websites, mobile applications, social media, as well as any other electronic, written, or oral communications. By submitting your information to CRF, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Donor Privacy Policy, as well as those stated in the CRF's Privacy Policy, incorporated herein by this reference, and to our using and processing the personal information for the purposes stated below.
CRF assures our donors, volunteers, and supporters that personal information will be handled with respect and with confidentiality to the extent provided by law.
Personal Information The information CRF collects and maintains includes, but is not limited to, the following types of personal information when it is voluntarily provided to us:
Contact information such as name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address
Gift giving information (including payment information)
Information on events attended, publications received and special requests for information related to CRF or its programs
Information provided in the form of comments and suggestions
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information CRF uses personal information to provide our donors, volunteers, and supporters with better service and with information about CRF's events and support/volunteer opportunities. Payment information collected is used only for donation or payment processing and is not retained for other purposes.  We protect the security of credit card transactions using a number of measures such as encryption, access controls, network firewalls, and physical security. These measures make it extremely difficult for anyone to intercept the credit card information you send to us. When we work with other companies to process credit card transactions, those companies also use encryption and other appropriate security measures.
CRF will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to third parties. Use of your personal information by CRF will be limited to internal purposes and only to further the organization’s activities.  We occasionally communicate with CRF donors on the behalf of third parties about activities we are also involved in and if the activity furthers CRF's mission. To opt out of receiving these types of communications, please contact our Development Manager (See Contact below).
Discontinuing Contact Upon Request CRF will discontinue or change the method used to contact any person, including donors, volunteers, and supporters, as soon as possible upon that person’s oral or written request.
CRF will maintain records of all requests for discontinuance of contact, whether written or oral, effective with the adoption of this Donor Privacy Policy. CRF will maintain records to the extent necessary for legal or liability purposes.
Changes to the Privacy Policy CRF reserves the right to update or modify this Donor Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Donor Privacy Policy on our website at crf-usa.org.
ContactIf you have questions about this Donor Privacy Policy, the of your personal information, and to change your change contact preferences, please contact our Development Manager or write us at:
Constitutional Rights FoundationAttention:  Development601 South Kingsley Dr.Los Angeles, CA 90005
Revised:  October 27, 2017
Remember Me
Log in
Sign in with FacebookSign in with GoogleSign in with Windows Live
Forgot Login?
Sign up
Thank you for a great publication. A fellow teacher pointed me to your Bill of Rights in Action publication. It's nice to have a resource that will put some depth to a topic without overwhelming the students.--Mr. Raj R., Teacher
Free subscription to Bill of Rights in Action.
Current subscribers - switch to electronic-only delivery and your copy will arrive up to 2 weeks before the printed issue.
Joomla3 Appliance - Powered by TurnKey Linux
